

SUHAIB AHMAD

UI / UX & Graphic Designer

An experienced individual who have what it takes to fulfill any of many positions related to multimedia jobs of graphic design & video production. Although web dev became my main profession, working with multimedia has never stopped. Currently, I am working as a freelance web dev based in Jordan and open for a full-time opportunity anywhere worldwide.

https://Suhaib.dev

SuhaibAhmadAi@hotmail.com

Makkahwi

() **(** +6011-280-94-804

😝 🧭 Makkahwi

Experiences

Graphic Designer

Part-Timer

QFM Malaysia | KL, Malaysia

6 Months Jun 2016 - Jun 2018

Graphic Designer

Part-Timer

SpeedWheels | KL, Malaysia

2 Months Jan - Feb 2017

PR Executive

Part-Timer

Mercy Mission | KL, Malaysia

7 Months Dec 2015 - Jun 2016

Media Bureau

Volunteering

PSA Malaysia | KL, Malaysia

17 Months Feb 2013 - Jun 2015

Video Editor

Freelancer

Malaysia

2 Months Oct 2019 - Nov 2019

Graphic Designer

Freelancer

Malaysia

4 Years Feb 2015 - Apr 2019

Skills

Ai

Illustrator



Photoshop



InDesign

Χd

Adobe XD



Premiere Pro

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science

International Islamic University Malaysia | May 2021

Specialized in Data Science and Computational Intelligence

Languages

Arabic

English

Malay

German

Mother Tongue

Professional

Daily-Life Basics

Daily-Life Basics